https://realhope.com/privacy-policy/

Expert Psychological Witness For Asylum & VAWA
Webinar Training For Psychological Evaluations For Use In Immigration Court
Expert Psychological Witness For Asylum & VAWA
Webinar Training For Psychological Evaluations For Use In Immigration Court
Pacific Skills Training Privacy Policy
THIS PRIVACY POLICY COVERS THE SITE https://realhope.com.
BECAUSE WE WANT TO DEMONSTRATE OUR COMMITMENT TO OUR USERS
PRIVACY, WE DISCLOSE THE FOLLOWING INFORMATION:
1. What personally identifiable information Pacific Skills Training Co. collects.
2. What personally identifiable information third parties collect through the Web site.
3. What organization collects the information.
4. How Pacific Skills Training Co. uses the information.
5. With whom Pacific Skills Training Co. may share user information.
6. What choices are available to users regarding collection, use and distribution of the information.
7. What types of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Pacific Skills Training Co. control. 8. How users can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE Pacific Skills Training Co. is the sole owner of the infomation collected on our web site. Pacific Skills Training Co. collects information at several different points on our Web site. Information is collected for the purpose of sending a Couples Communication Skills Tips email.   Frequency will be once a week.  Also used for customer satisfaction follow-up evaluation of service/product’s usefulness, for opt-in notification.   A user must provide the clickstream information (internet protocol address, internet service provider, platform type, date/time stamp, operating system), http protocol information (last uri requested and browser type), interaction information (browser interaction such as when the mouse moves over an image), state management mechanisms (data allowing a user to be tracked consistently), user’s name, user’s login information, user’s identity certificate and user’s home contact information.  The reason we use this information is to complete the current transaction, contact by email or regular mail and enhance our site and product offerings.   We retain this information as stated by our business practices.  When users have data collected for the purpose of contacting by email or regular mail, they are given the opportunity to opt-out of information collected (Please see our Choice and Opt-out section).
COOKIES A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates.  A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user’s hard drive for an extended period of time.   Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions.  You can set your browser to notify you to either accept or deny the cookie according to the following information.   Our website uses cookies to enhance our site.
PROFILES Pacific Skills Training Co. does not create a user profile.
COMMUNICATIONS FROM THE SITE When customers provide us contact information for Website (users can opt-out by following the directions in our ‘Choice’ section) we use the information to contact the user to deliver sales and product information that will be useful to the them.
Sharing Information
Legal Disclaimer Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.
Personally Identifiable Information
Information collected for Website is shared with United States Postal Service (users have the option of not submitting data to this recipient.   Information collected for Website is shared with United States Postal Service (users have the option of not submitting data to this recipient. Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable) Information collected for Website is shared with United States Postal Service and (users have the option of not submitting data to this recipien.   Information collected for Website is shared with United States Postal Service and (users have the option of not submitting data to this recipient.
